<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pepper_Hotel</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="About_us">
        The Emirates Grand Hotel in Dubai is ideally situated on Sheikh Zayed Road known as "The Heart of Dubai",
        which is considered the business hub and shopping mecca of Dubai.The hotel is a brief fifteen minutes away from Dubai International Airport, Emirates Road, Expo Centre, and Dubai Convention Centre, Emirate of Sharjah,
        and a short walking distance from Dubai\'s largest mall including The Dubai Mall. We have 340 rooms in our hotel.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_facilities">
        "Here are the Amenities provided by Hotel "
    </string>
    <string name="rooms">
        The Deluxe Room Featuring a modern decor, this spacious air-conditioned room comes with a flat-screen satellite TV and a mini bar.
        \nStart From Aed 160 Per Day
        \nRoom Size – 34 sq m
    </string>
    <string name="room3">
        This spacious suite features a living room with flat-screen TV, DVD player, iPod docking station and panoramic view of Dubai city.
        It includes a bathroom with luxury toiletries and a separate tub. Room Size – 35 sq m
        \nStart From Aed 180 Per Day

    </string>
    <string name="room4">
        This Junior spacious suite comes with a 37-inch flat screen TV, DVD player and iPod docking station.
        It includes a private bathroom stocked with luxury toiletries.
        \nStart From Aed 350 Per Day
        \nRoom Size – 57 sq m
    </string>
    <string name="dining">
        At The Emirates Grand Hotel\'s Café and Restaurant, you will discover a selection of exquisite delicacies to enjoy throughout the day. Indulge in gourmet snacks,
        sandwiches, delightful pastries, ice creams, cakes, aromatic coffee, freshly squeezed juice, smoothies,
        fusion tea, and mocktails. The hotel\'s international all-day dining restaurant offers an extensive buffet for breakfast and lunch,
        whether it\'s a business meeting, a social gathering, or simply quality time spent with your loved ones.
    </string>
</resources>